the race is not visible at all,
раса не видно вообще
but
а
looks like a good afternoon, your wine is the coat of arms of the USSR
похож на добрый день ваша вина герб ссср
.
.
who are you a blogger
на кого вы блогер
no you don’t really admit to
нет очень не признаетесь
know all Russians are more gracious no I wasn’t
знаешь все русские благодатней нет я не
if I’m a blogger from Ukraine andrey pop
был если я блогер из украины андрей pop
it’s
она
just there if I meet a blog yes I
просто есть если я встречаю блоге да я с
talk to him like a blogger I’m not interested
ним говорю как с блоггером не интересно
in dishes from the forest just a person already
с блюдами из леса просто человек уже
part is just a person
часть просто человеком
I’ll start with a simple one for you, a blogger or a
начну с простого на вы блогер или
simple
простой
simple nightly
простого ночным
define the sectors, just see if
определим сектора просто смотрите если
there are bloggers who communicate
есть блогеры которые там общаются право
there right to tell people there that
ему там рассказывают людям что там
Ukraine has been bombing the Donbass for 8 years, I’ve been with them
украина 8 лет бомбила донбасс я с ними
one by one, that is, they’ve
по одному а то есть сразу
said serious facts at once, if it’s
серьезные по фактам сам наговорили если
just people then  we can just
просто люди то можем просто так
swing it a little bit
раскачивать немножко это
say yes the name of the channel
скажете да название канала
[laugh
[смех]
] look at
вот смотрите
your personal position
ваша личная позиция
because it’s happening in ukraine that this is a
потому что происходит в украине что это
war a special operation to continue to give
война спецоперация дальше давать
where the legs grow just to understand they want
откуда ноги растут просто понять хотят
to give them in what year the capos they
отдавать их в какой год капо им
managed 1001 2001 this is a good cop to me
удалось 1001 2001 у это хороший коп мне
I wonder what will be there, let's
интересно что там будет давайте
what events of
какие события
this salad, what to someone, what everyone
этого салата что кому то что каком все
wants, this is extended like Russia about  the
хотят это продлен как россия очень
borders are very close you understand and less than
близко границ сами понимаете и меньше
me it seems to me to be they don’t understand the
моего мне кажется ними быть не понимаю
real understanding
реальный понимая
america already mind america has a border with
америка уже уме у америки есть граница с
russia
россией
[music]
[музыка]
minutes i’m infuriated by the border with russia
минут у меня бесит граница с россией
directly there is america with
непосредственно имеется америке с
russia
россией
okay what did you do it
ладно а что у вас делали это
two thousand american
две тысячи американских войск на
what year the troops stop in 2015 the fifteenth
каком году прекращает 2015 пятнадцатом
year can you like this document and now I’m
году можете как это документ и вот мне
wondering where we got the dviglo
интересно откуда у нас взялись двигло
good 2 will visit me let
хорошо 2 меня посетит давайте чтобы я
’s hear for the first time honestly for the first time hearing
впервые услышал честно впервые услышав
that we have two thousand American
что у нас две тысячи американских войск
troops in Ukraine detail back and but
находится в украине деталь назад и но
now it’s in Russia  yes,
сейчас находится россии американцев да
how many thousands of Americans, and you can drag it with American
сколько тысяч и тащить это американских
troops as long as they are already like
можете пока они уже как
let's do it, you can now tell me
давайте так вы можете мне сейчас сказать
which one, at least from the news, even
какой то я хотя бы из новостей даже
Russian, I'll look where in the Russian
российских посмотрю где в российских
news of the border to present two thousand
новостях границы предъявить две тысячи
citizens
граждан
, the former American general is in captivity of
генерал бывший американский это в плену
ours, who let me  now
наш кто давайте я вот сейчас
thousands of American military and
тысяч американских военных и
American are
американских
getting better  Literally,
налаживается круто буквально
I learn so many new
я столько нового узнаю
things, I wonder what kind of American general the
интересно что за американский генерал
former coven, and even the
шабаш бывшие а уж и
mother of at least the former
мать хотя бы бывшего
now
сейчас
our volume, they give a call to a friend in the
наш тома под много передают звонок другу
western zone, I want to fly,
западную зону хочу лететь еще
it was real,
это было реально было
these were you, next time, prepare to
эти вы на следующий раз подготовитесь
look, then you will tell people this, I
поищите потом будете людям сказать это я
just
просто
maybe three months
может месяца три навыка вот
ago there was a general three years ago and now in
это три назад был генерал а теперь
short they cleared out information about him
короче зачистили информацию про него
here
сюда
2000 both military and American
2000 и военных и американских
if you took two thousand American
если вы взяли две тысячи американских
military generals in the exam already and
военных генералов экзамене уже и
American
американским
American citizens and two
навернутой американских граждан и две
thousand citizens of America, let's say the
тысячи граждан америки давайте
United States where in her pocket
соединенных штатов где в кармане ней
former former and kind where the aristarchus took
бывшие бывшего и рода где аристарх взяла
two thousand American citizens captive in the
две тысячи американских граждан плен
fields
полях
against
против
let's finish with the Americans
давайте мы закончим с американцами
let's move on okay
перейдем дальше ладно давайте
let's get the information in the wrong place about the American
информации не туда про американского
general and two thousand American
генерала и две тысячи американских
mercenaries
наёмников
experts take an extra minute
знатоки берут дополнительную минуту
alexander friend who will give an answer
александр друзь кто будет давать ответ
I love these moments that to  when
я люблю эти моменты которые когда гора
I’ll find the mountain right now and, in short, already an idiot 2-3
щас найду и короче уже идиотом 2-3
minutes I found everything in the ward
минуты всё нашёл палате
what should I type in google yu tube
что мне набрать в гугле ю тубе
1 admiral suite to the director himself admiral to the
1 адмирал люкс директору сам-то адмирал
rector admiral this is the fleet yes this is the city of the
ректору адмирал это флот да это город
world logo roll rick kashin take it
мира logo ролл рик кашин заберите это
just google even about the goose
просто гуглите даже про за гуся
amerikashki general hit pin russia
америкашки генерал попал пин россия
russian general
русский генерал
captive in
плен в мариуполе
mariupol thriller co2 generators mineral daddy
триллер генераторы co2 минерал папа
films of russia let's be the
пленки россии давайте
first to beautifully 1 the site writes to me the current
первым 1 мне пишет сайт действующий
denal for that I got
денал на то попался
what the [ __ ] well here's a bunch show me where
какой нафиг ну вот куча покажите мне где
you can watch the video with this general
можно видео с этим генералом посмотреть
let
давайте
me type as you said  here the
я набрал так как вы сказали вот
American general was captured
американский генерал попал в плен
beautiful and
красивы и
our love and it is written that this is a fake
наша любовь и написано что это фейк
day, then you can take photos of how he is
суток то можно фотографий как его берут
taken prisoner video where to take but I
в плен видео где взять а вот видео я
will show you the 5th
покажу вам 5
place
место не будут смотрите вы мне скажете я
variant released Normans 1000
валюту и я вариант выпущен норманны 1000
don't worry strikes tell me the
не буду волнуйтесь страйки скажите мне
name I'll pick up from the cemetery
название я наберусь от кладбища
let's take the quality of the doses
давайте возьмем по качеству доз
live
проживать
[muses  ka]
[музыка]
I don’t see you black screen
я вас не вижу черный экран
somewhere the camera was switched
где-то камеру переключили
I don’t see and don’t hear you
я вас не вижу и не слышу
well,
ну
what is the true type of display you are a vidos and
что истинных тип показа ты видос и что
something doesn’t work
то не получается
if you I don’t hear you and I don’t see you I
если вы я вас не слышу и не вижу вижу
just see a black screen
просто черный экран
somewhere the camera was switched  it doesn’t
где-то камеру переключили она не
show if I hear it,
показываю если у меня слышите это
switch back the
переключите назад
problem is to say the name of the video,
проблема сказать название ролика я
I would open it now and watch
сейчас бы его открыл и посмотрел
you heard me
вы меня слышали
before that, wait, mind, it turns out
до этого не так подожди ума получается я
I didn’t see or hear you, the black screen
вас и не видел и не слышал черный экран
was and didn’t hear and
был и не слышал и
don’t hear wait  a minute it’s just me
не слышат ща подождите минуту меня
and a butterfly
и бабочка
I switched
я переключилась
shorter
короче
with a general shorter the peasant didn’t
с генералом короче у мужика не
succeed so there were three news of the
получилось так что там было три новости
day
дня
I remember the Galatians 3 months ago it was the step of the
я помню галатам 3 месяце тому было шагом
French NATO generals the roof and
французских натовские генералов крыша и
there it was shorter so then all Mariupol
там короче было так тогда все мариуполь
took from all there then show us the video
из всех там взяли то покажите нам видос
before the general there, I took the yak of an American
до генерала там як американского
general and, in short, I took two thousand
генерала взял и короче як там две тысячи
American moments there, shorter than the
американских моменте взяла короче
Russians and with a flagellum from such on the necks of
россиян и жгутиком из таких на шейках
the old ones themselves, so throw them on
старинных самых собой так вот им
enter the elevator and orders in three
накинуть войти в лифт и велит через три
days already the process is forgotten, so that is, for a
дня уже процесс забывают так то есть
century everyone is exposed
веке все разоблачаются
lecture and
лекцию и
mana on prices clamp them to think of new
маны на цены зажать их загадывать новой
Russian propaganda in
российской пропаганды в
dial I will
наберу я
find now I will find now I am an
сейчас найду сейчас найду вот я
artist and the moment for and 1 of my love
художница и момент на и 1 своих любовных
games in chat roulette  I’ll find it now
игр в чат-рулетке это сейчас найду
subscribe to the channel
подписывайтесь на канал
put likes
ставти лайки
overestimate and comments and
завышают и комментарии и
would go home ruhats whole information
бы домой рухаты целую информационную
guilt would be given by the words cry
вину дали слова cry